offspring.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy: The Offspring

The Offspring understand the privacy concerns of visitors to our website. We have created this privacy statement to explain what information we collect from your visit to Offspring.com, how that information is used, and the choices you have regarding the collection and use of such information. 

## Use of Certain Information

As a general practice, we do not automatically collect personally identifiable information (such as your name, mailing address or e-mail address) from your visit to our site. We only gather personal information from visitors to our site if that information is voluntarily submitted. However, certain non-personal information (such as the type of browser and operating system being used, and your IP address), is recorded by our servers when you visit our site. This information is collected so we can provide you with a more personalized interactive experience on our site.

Depending on the activities on Offspring.com in which you choose to participate, we may request that you provide us with certain information about yourself in order to participate in those activities. Our registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact information (such as your name, mailing address and e-mail address), demographic information (such as your age and gender) and profile data (such as your preferences in entertainment). This information may be used by us and may be shared with our affiliates, subsidiaries and promotional partners for marketing and promotional purposes. On occasion, we may use your contact information to send you information about our products and services, and about us and what we’re doing. We will not sell or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties, and will not use your personally identifiable information in any way other than as provided in this privacy statement.

If you request information, products or services through our site, we may use order forms to collect contact information (such as your name, mailing address and e-mail address) and, when appropriate, financial information (such as your credit card number), to process your request. Contact information from an order form may be used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding your order. Any financial information collected to process your request will not be shared with third parties who are not involved with the transaction.

We will disclose information gathered from Offspring.com when required by law or upon the request of a law enforcement agency. We may also disclose user information in cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

## Use of Cookies and IP Addresses

Cookies are files containing information about a user that a website transfers to a user’s hard drive. We use cookies to enhance the user’s experience on this site by, among other things, saving user passwords and preferences. The cookies we place on a user’s hard drive are used only in connection with our site and do not contain personal information unless the user provides that information to us. If you do not want websites to be able to store cookies on your hard drive, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. However, disabling the use of cookies may affect the proper functioning of the site or may slow down the site considerably.

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider when you are surfing the Web. When you access Offspring.com, our servers log your IP address. We collect and use IP addresses to gather information on the use of our site, analyze trends, administer the site, and to aggregate demographic information. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

## Chat Areas and Bulletin Boards

Users of Offspring.com are solely responsible for the content of messages they post on our site, such as in any chat rooms or bulletin boards which may be supported by the site. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information on bulletin boards or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited contacts from other people.

Each user who wishes to participate in any chat room or bulletin board which may be supported on this site must provide an e-mail address in addition to the user’s screen name. We request those e-mail addresses in order to protect the security and integrity of Offspring.com, including taking action against users who post inappropriate material or harass other users.

## Links to Other Sites

Offspring.com is linked to websites operated by other companies. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites, and we recommend that you read the privacy statements of each website that you link to through us. This privacy statement applies only to the information collected by this site.

## Security

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We strive to ensure the security of the information that you submit to us, and we have implemented various procedures to safeguard your personal information. Among other things, we use encryption software to protect the transmission of credit card information, and we require agents and contractors related to our site to comply with our online privacy policy. However, data transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or that is transmitted to you, and you do so at your own risk.

## Information for Parents Concerning Privacy

We operate Offspring.com in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to this Site without the knowledge and permission of a parent or guardian. If we determine that a user is under the age of 13, we will not maintain or use any personal information about such user without the consent of a parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. If we cannot maintain or use personal information about a user under the age of 13, that user will not be able to participate in some activities on the site.

In order to comply with the act, we do not request personal information from children other than information that is reasonably necessary in order for children to participate in activities on this site. If particular information is requested in connection with a certain activity, we do not retain this information after the activity is completed and do not use it for any other purpose.

In certain circumstances, we may ask users to provide us with a parent’s or guardian’s contact information. This information will only be used to contact that parent or guardian to notify them of a child’s participation in an activity on Offspring.com, to notify the parent or guardian of our privacy and information practices with respect to children and/or to seek the consent of the parent or guardian to the child’s participation in an activity on this site.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our privacy practices or this site, please [info@offspring.com](mailto:info@offspring.com "E-mail info@liberationmedia.com").

Information provided by you via general inquiries to the above address is used only to respond to your inquiries and is not shared with outside parties.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

Your use of Offspring.com signifies your acceptance of our privacy policies. Please do not use our site if you do not accept our privacy policies. As we may change or update our privacy policies at any time, please review this statement from time to time. Your continued use of this site following any changes to our privacy policies posted in this statement indicates your consent to those changes.
